[Music]
I can't believe all this is here an
Imperium we were always taught the
wildness was nothing but lava pools and
gross melons the lava wastes are but one
region of my land there are many others
Diamond glaciers the forever Rock
boiling Beach and here the forest of
spirits
you self-obsessed imperion never thought
you'd have to deal with anything beyond
your own borders but now after the merge
no one can ignore what's right outside
their
[Applause]
[Music]
door what is that our destination
H give it to
[Music]
me
according to the Ancients of my land
these doors were sealed long ago
intended to never be opened except by
the power of a source Dragon that's why
you had me keep some of that Source
dragon energy exactly Imperium has
crumbled but my ultimate plans have not
and now I will accomplish what no one
has for centuries I shall harness The
Forbidden secrets of this
Temple hold on not all of us have your
natural night
[Music]
[Applause]
vision behold the key to unlocking the
dark powers of a lost age when the blood
moon arrives we will assemble the most
powerful beings in the merged Realms
then no one will be able to stop
us l in me and know so much to see
Together We will
rise
[Music]
wein
up here bolts for
[Music]
brains
[Applause]
[Music]
it's okay Fuji Dove I got you oh loo not
again
[Music]
hey look at
that hey it's your girl ninja fan
infinity and me it's Spinjitsu for days
999 like And subscribe we're coming at
you from the site of the Ninja's latest
Victory they just saved three people on
this street corner from an out of
control race in
back new ninja classic ninja working
together love it don't forget to smash
that like button and don't forget our
ninja
merch sure the ninja are back some of
them but where are the others Master woo
Cole Jay pixel still lost in the merge
no one's asking these smart Brave
questions except me intelligent George
up next more activ from the mysterious
night ghost but first quick shout out to
the sponsor of today's video Bal
sufficient nutrient Wafers enough
nutrition to suffice no distracting
taste not just for pet turtles
anymore what's going on bad
connection what the
Sora just practicing my Elemental Tech
Powers now that I can do them without
ru's help this is a whole new world for
me must be nice look Aaron just because
you don't have elemental powers doesn't
mean you're not vital to the team I know
I know Lloyd tells me all the time you
shouldn't be watching that so-called
intelligent George guy anyway everything
he says is made up you're right but
sometimes he talks about people that
went missing in the merage like my
parents did I have to find them but
there's no information anywhere so some
sometimes I get so desperate I watch
intelligent George a man who insists the
moon is made of donut I have no doubt
we'll find your parents someday but you
need a break obsessing like this isn't
good for your mental health how about we
hit the courtyard and and flex those
ninja skills and rayu can try flying
again I always like how you think
Sora
oh no how many times have I told them
rayu has gotten too big to run through
these
Halls you're making a mess of the place
again we'll clean it all up promise
someone came to see you two while you
were out they left a
note thank
you oh come on
who is it
from creel of all people it says she has
urgent need of ninja assistance then the
weirdest part is it signed your friend
creel you think she meant to give this
to someone else she probably just wants
to sell us some junk from her
[Music]
junkyard
Lloyd what
where am
I sleeping in the training course oh
right sure of
course everything all right never
[Music]
better eat that Nindroid I am not
consuming any food it's a figure of
speech it's what you say when you're
kicking someone's butt in the game but
eating is a good thing how is that
insulting to me oh
[Music]
sane oh tea I could really use some Hey
Lloyd you uh trying a new way to drink
[Music]
tea oh man what am I
doing H it appears your body's vital
operations are under fatigue huh you are
over tired have you been having
difficulty sleeping what me no sleeping
like a baby well maybe you ought to
crawl into your crib for a nap buddy
yeah maybe you're
[Music]
right
what
oh man that was the worst one
yet my nightmares are getting worse
Uncle like I'm being haunted I don't
know if Aaron why are you awake I was
going to ask you the same thing can't
sleep worrying about my parents can't
stop thinking about them ever since I
saw them in the merge Quake battle then
I heard a loud noise come from your room
I kind of had a nightmare are you okay
everyone's noticed how strange you've
been acting lately really I thought I
was hiding it pretty
well okay look I've been having dreams
that are so vivid so frightening I hate
to sleep I've never experienced anything
like them maybe they're tied to that
Source Dragon I was a conduit for but I
haven't been able to find any
information about Source dragons
anywhere you've been through a lot like
saving the entire merged Realms it would
make sense that all that tension is
coming out in stress
dreams huh aren't I supposed to be the
teacher
here listen young one dreams can never
hurt you for they are not
real well if I didn't know better I'd
think Master woo was right next to
me let's get some rest I'm sure you're
right there's nothing to be afraid
of I can't make sense out of any of this
what language are these Scrolls even
written in thexan it is an age-old
language baned centuries ago when it's
users had grown too powerful then how
are we supposed to learn all these
supposed ancient Secrets patience as my
master taught me true power takes
time what's happening is this a trap no
it's another one of my
recruits and as you can see my security
Bots are no
help the dogs don't even bark and they
are super
vicious super vicious they must sense
how nice you are I did make them pies
once whoever's been breaking in here has
found a way to do it without being
noticed and what has this thief stolen
that's just it
nothing did you ever think that I don't
know if the alarms aren't being set off
or the dogs aren't barking and nothing's
missing then maybe no one's actually
breaking in of course someone is they
leave this place a mess when I come back
in the
morning um it always looks like
this I have a personal organizational
system that no one understands but me
trust me someone's been breaking in here
and rifling through my
stuff maybe this is the work of the
night ghost He department stores for
revenge against Bad return policies is
that some intelligent George thing Aaron
that stuff is totally made up yeah I
realized how silly it sounded as soon as
I said it out loud I'm certain all these
break-ins are due to me going upscale
excuse me upscale I've Diversified the
junkyard it's not just used Mech parts
anymore I now have antique weapons
ancient artifacts and rare Treasures
lots more money to be made with those of
course besides I hear my class he joined
isn't the only one getting hit so I
trust you'll find the Intruder what's
the point of being best friends with two
ninja if you can't get a little help now
and again huh best friends of course
ever since you joined the ninja I've
been telling everyone what great friends
we are from our old days Mech racing
together we were enemies yeah I'm pretty
sure you rigged our Mech to explode H
those those fond memories are only
making me more nostalgic for our time
together selfie say creel's junkyard
creel's
junkyard ooh my hat looks juny this pick
is going to get even more likes than
that Lobo Fail video I posted two of the
newest Ninja were recently seen at
creel's junkyard was this a social visit
between longtime best friends or were
they investigating the work of the night
ghost subscribe why are you watching
that you're the one who said intelligent
George makes it all up his theory that
there's a ghost haunting department
stores because of return policy
vengeance is absurd but as much as
admitting it makes my skin crawl creel's
right there have been other break-ins an
intelligent George is wrong none of the
places broken into were department
stores they were all places that sell
antiques like K's junkyard but nothing
was stolen not yet my guess is someone
is looking for a very particular ancient
artifact but who and why be so sneaky
and weird about it should we tell the
others no this might turn out to be
nothing and from the sound of it Lloyd
needs his rest but you me and rayu up
for a field
[Music]
trip
no
luck that's the last of the places
around here that carry old artifacts and
each one had the same story someone
broke in somehow didn't set off any
alarms and then didn't end up taking
anything maybe there is a ghost doing
this we've been to every antique shop we
know about the only way to get whoever's
doing this is to catch them in the ACT
but where will they hit next Ru where
are you
going you seriously ran off just because
you smelled food he's a teenage Dragon
he has three settings running sleeping
eating but we can get food back at all
realm antique imporium grand opening
sale Sora I think we might have just
found the night ghost's next
Target it's closed for the night which
means we have to to stake it out rayu
let's stock up on some steak out
[Applause]
[Music]
noodles you know last time you hid rayu
in a dumpster he got discovered captured
and hand it over to an evil dragon
draining Empress exactly what are the
odds of that happening
[Music]
twice is it the night ghost if it is
she's definitely breaking the evil
villain
[Music]
stereotype H people throwing out
perfectly good dragons shameful what are
we going to do if the night ghost does
show up antique shops aren't known for
stocking the kind of tech I can use my
powers on at least you have powers Aaron
you can do Spinjitsu I can't sure a real
wonky version of it but no matter how
hard I train I don't get any better and
you know my Spinjitsu throw when I put
Spinjitsu into an object I still can't
figure out how that
works remember what Lloyd said no one's
ninja journey is the same so far my
inability to do Spinjitsu hasn't been a
problem but I should be better than I am
when I find my parents I want them to be
so proud of what I've
become hey where did he come from
there's no way he can get him without
breaking the door
down is that the elemental master of
[Music]
smoke Mr frohickey why are you up so
late oh you know just fixing the mess of
two young ninja and their pet dragon
even though they Pro promised they'd
clean it up themselves where are they
they really should be the ones to clean
up they told me that they had an
important steak out and would fix it
tomorrow but I don't believe cleaning
should ever wait Steak
Out finally don't
move ah the ninja I was warned you might
catch on to me eventually you're
outnumbered
surrender you thought I came
[Music]
alone not sure what you want with that
thing but I'm guessing it isn't to start
a drum circle with your masked buddies
here you don't know me kid maybe
percussion is my
thing
get that to Lord Raz I'll handle these
three
R not so fast
[Music]
kid Aaron get that Mallet if Lord Ross
wants it it must be for something
terrible
[Music]
you threw a party and didn't invite
me I'm
offended
wolf
mask Lloyd are you okay come on let's
get out of
[Music]
here it's not a dream it's real
it's all real the blood moon is coming
the blood moon is
coming finally found it Lord and now our
dark Journey can begin are you
ready prepare to feel power like you've
never known
[Music]
before